

+86 186 1628 6042

swawrzyn@gmail.com

www.gostefan.com

# **ABOUT ME**

After 10 years in the military I decided it was time for a new adventure. I decided on Asia and went to Taiwan to learn Chinese.

I enjoy the problem-solving aspect of programming, and relish the opportunity to learning something new and expanding my skill set.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English – Native Polish – Fluent French – Intermediate Chinese – Intermediate

### **EDUCATION**

Le Wagon Shanghai, China 2018

Full Stack Web Development

National Taiwan Normal University Taipei, Taiwan 2015 - 2016

Contemporary Chinese

Royal Military College of Canada *Kingston, Canada*  2005 - 2009

**BA** Business Administration

# STEFAN WAWRZYN

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Solution seeking coder with a wide set of skills and experience. Passionate about building structurally sound, interesting and easy to use applications for all users. Seeking new challenges as part of a team of dynamic individuals.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

**Server-side:** Python, Ruby, Django, Java, FastAPI,

Flask, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Redis

**Client-side:** Typescript, Javascript, Vue.js, CSS, HTML, WeChat, Flutter, Tailwind

**Development and** AWS, Docker, CI/CD, TDD, pytest, Git,

**Operations:** Selenium, Cypress

SKILLS:

Leadership KPI Teamwork Self Project
Management Management Management

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Lead Developer**

2021/06 - Present | Eqlaim - Shanghai, China

Co-founded and developed a Business Interruption insurance claim management system using FastAPI and Vue.js.

#### **Computer Science Teacher**

2018/09 - 2019/10 | Shanghai High Tech Creative School - Shanghai, China Taught a High School AP-certified Computer Science course to multiple grade levels.

 Developed and taught a curriculum in Java and Python teaching OOP basics while injecting side projects in AI/ML, web and mobile app development.

# **Lead Developer**

2019/04 - 2021/04 | DuanDuanZu - Shanghai, China Co-founded and built a AirBnB-esque system for commercial spaces in Shanghai.

 Built with Django on the backend, Vue.js on the frontend and a mobile applet in the WeChat ecosystem. Built fully within a TDD mindset while using CI/CD onto AWS services.

## **English Teacher - Game Developer**

2017/06 - 2018/09 | K&H International School - Shanghai, China

Taught children from ages 3 to 10 the fundamentals of the English language.

• Developed a small JavaScript based game in the Unity engine to facilitate student recognition and retention of key vocabulary.

#### **Armour Officer**

2011/01 – 2015/08 | Canadian Armed Forces – Edmonton, Canada

An Armoured Officer for 6 years, I acted in many roles ranging from Troop Leader in charge of 4 tank crews, to Course Officer where I was responsible for over 120 personnel in training the next-generation of tank commanders.